<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/search.json?base_query=&amp;city=&amp;country=&amp;county=&amp;facets%5B%5D=location&amp;facets%5B%5D=business_category&amp;facets%5B%5D=category&amp;facets%5B%5D=schedule_type_id&amp;facets%5B%5D=employee_class&amp;facets%5B%5D=normalized_location&amp;facets%5B%5D=job_function_id&amp;latitude=&amp;loc_group_id=&amp;loc_query=United+States&amp;longitude=&amp;offset=1530&amp;query_options=&amp;radius=24km&amp;region=&amp;result_limit=10&amp;sort=relevant</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>850f0199e2ce9d1d51ee5e2e11318d94</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986897/software-development-engineer-i</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer I</title>
      <description>Amazon’s Global Logistics Technology team is chartered with building solutions for international movement of shipments which can originate from any place on earth, cross the international border and be delivered in a different part of planet. There are variety of ways in which we can import shipments from vendors/sellers to our warehouses and export package from one country to another through several intermediate locations to deliver it to our international customer. There are millions of such packages, each with different attributes, delivery requirements and international commerce and customs constraints. What results is a complex graph of source, intermediate and destination nodes with their arcs crossing international borders and associated with different costs and transit times. Accounting for all these constraints and maximizing the number of shipments shipped, while minimizing cost, providing a variety of customer delivery options and maximizing delivery performance is our primary focus.We are building world class technology cutting across deep algorithmic problems, brand new tools that cater to multi-party business scenarios and challenging data models that are evolving very quickly. Our systems touch every single package that travels internationally which mandates building of highly available and scalable distributed systems. Besides technology, there are ample opportunities in the team to build domain expertise of international transportation and supply chain realms and get first-hand experience of the Amazon operations by interacting directly with our global internal and external partners, and of course the esteemed senior engineering talent pool.We are looking for highly talented software development engineers who are passionate not only about architecting and developing large scale distributed technology solutions but also innovating new ideas and providing directions to our business in the domain of imports and exports logistics. We have many key initiatives lined-up to support our rapid evolution and growth of cross border transportation network by solving some of the most challenging problems in this domain.#AGLT</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>986897</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>9215700a26684c9dca1ad77718f33ff2</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986896/business-intelligence-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Business Intelligence Engineer</title>
      <description>Amazon Advertising is dedicated to driving measurable outcomes for brand advertisers, agencies, authors, and entrepreneurs. Our ad solutions—including sponsored, display, video, and custom ads—leverage Amazon’s innovations and insights to find, attract, and engage intended audiences throughout their daily journeys. With a range of flexible pricing and buying models, including self-service, managed service, and programmatic ad buying, these solutions help businesses build brand awareness, increase product sales, and more.We are seeking an exceptional Business Intelligence Engineer to join the Advertising Forecasting Science team at Palo Alto, California. You will have extremely high visibility via presenting regular business metrics to leadership on a regular basis, and work closely with a group of talented scientists and engineers. You will need to dive deep into distributed data at the Petabyte level and provide insights to guide the development of Machine Learning problems in time series and revenue forecasts, auction prediction, and bid optimizations, to support the growth of Amazon’s advertising business.Our ideal candidate will have strong analytical skills, business acumen and judgement, intellectual curiosity, technical skills, and excel at both written and verbal communications. S/he will be a self-motivated individual who is comfortable with ambiguity and be able to think critically about a science product from business standpoint.The primary responsibilities of this role include:· Design, develop, and maintain scalable, automated metrics reports and dashboards to support our analytical and business needs· Provide insights on data analytics to influence model development roadmap· Work closely with stakeholders and leadership to define and present the team’s business operational metrics· Work closely with scientists to define and present the team’s model-related metrics· Recognize and adopt best practices in reporting and analytics – automation, data integrity, validation, and documentation</description>
      <location>US, CA, Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Business Intelligence</category>
      <job_id>986896</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>14b00d40ced925890eb4eca458040133</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986894/senior-solution-design-manager</job_url>
      <title>Senior Solution Design Manager</title>
      <description>The Amazon Cross Border Exports team is looking for a highly skilled and motivated Sr. Solution Design Manager to incubate a supply chain execution team. The role and the team will be responsible for onboarding logistics partners as part of our Cross-Border expansion plans. The successful candidate will work closely with both internal and external stakeholders to drive and program manage logistics execution programs.An ideal candidate has a background in transportation or logistics/operations management and excellent data driven problem resolution skills. This person will have the ability to leverage and analyze data and blend that with experience to lead process improvements, standardize team processes and eliminate the root cause of defects. This job will require exceptional team leadership, communication and interpersonal skills while having the ability to in a high pressure environment and exercise sound judgment. The successful candidate will be proficient at strategic problem solving, prioritizing logistics challenges and possess a bias to get things done and deliver results while attracting, growing and retaining a highly talented team.Key responsibilities for 2019/20 include· Work with cross-functional teams to on-board carriers to support AGL global initiatives· Build, own and incubate a repeatable process/function which can be handed off to a team of program managers as we scale· Contribute to strategic yearly planning processes</description>
      <location>US, WA, Bellevue</location>
      <category>Supply Chain/Transportation Management</category>
      <job_id>986894</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>0c96a59282dc24bbc546bf31d42825d5</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986893/instock-manager</job_url>
      <title>Instock Manager</title>
      <description>The AmazonFresh and Prime Now organizations are at the forefront of developing and supporting the future of grocery and ultra-fast delivery services at Amazon. Our passion is driving an excellent customer experience in the grocery space by optimizing existing business functions and inventing solutions for previously unsolved problems. We are hiring an Instock Manager who invents and simplifies to solve complex problems, excels at querying and analyzing data to dive deep, and isn't afraid to roll up his/her sleeves to deliver results.The Instock Manager will be responsible for executing inventory strategies to optimize customer experience, sales, margin and turns. They will be relentlessly focused on delivering high in-stock rates in order to meet the needs of our customers. They will dive deep core drivers of in-stock performance, and proactively identify opportunities to improve tools and work flows. This role interacts closely with retail and operations business partners across Amazon, and is pivotal to the growth of this strategic initiative.Specific responsibilities include:· Manage inventory availability and inventory health including improved in-stock, turns, vendor operational improvement (efficiency, fill rates, lead time), forecasting, and shrink· Drive strategic initiatives to improve customer experience, enable new capabilities, and reduce waste· Answer complex business questions and make decisions by querying and analyzing large data sets· Work with internal teams to build automated tools and process improvements that will drive scale and reduce error· Manage day-to-day operational relationships with vendors and distributors partners, including product lifecycle management, expanding selection and optimize sourcing recommendations / decisions· Liaison between product categories teams, internal operations business partners and vendor partners· Maintain vendor relationship and work on vendor performance improvement through daily communication, training session, tracking purchase orders, investigating late deliveries, resolving order rejections, working with vendors on PO automation, etc.· Determination of order quantities by taking into account forecasts, historical trends and inventory targets</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Buying, Planning, &amp; Instock Management</category>
      <job_id>986893</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>fff278b8672d6999631c5517c081fc4d</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986891/shift-manager-logistics</job_url>
      <title>Shift Manager, Logistics</title>
      <description>Do you want to work hard, have fun and make history? If you do then Amazon could be the right career choice for you. Our logistics teams are changing the way we interact with customers around the globe every single day and solving some of the biggest logistical challenges facing not just Amazon, but also the entire industry.Amazon’s transportation teams work to ensure the delivery packages globally for customers around the world. On its busiest day, Cyber Monday,Amazon customers around the world have ordered more than 400 items per second and the transportation teams play a critical role ensuring packages make it to customers’ doors on-time and in great condition. Whether its items large or small, we find solutions to make sure we are delivering on our promise for customers.Our Area Managers are responsible for the day-to-day operations of delivery stations in the Amazon network, including inbound, outbound, and sortation operations. They will actively engage with site and regional operations leadership to implement new operational improvements and new services. We expect our managers to continually identify ways to improve our operations.Key Job Duties· Oversee the delivery of Amazon orders to customers· Build, optimize, and assign delivery routes on your shift· Communicate with and respond to Amazon Customer Service associates on delivery exceptions and requests· Support Amazon operations leadership team in daily operations management of the delivery station, including route assignment, leading meetings, and communicating with internal and external suppliers.· Troubleshoot problems through to resolution, escalating as necessary· Provide vacation coverage for other managers· Review and update SOPs as required· Participate in Lean/Kaizen, Black Belt, and other Operational Excellence initiatives• Ensure compliance throughout the site to global process standards and work on continuous improvement initiativesAdditional Job Elements:• Must be able to lift up to 49 pounds with or without reasonable accommodation• Must be willing and able to frequently push, pull, squat, bend, and reach• Must be able to stand/walk for up to 10-12 hours• Must be able to work in an environment where the noise level varies and can be loud• Must be able to work in an environment where the temperature may vary between 60 and 90 degrees, and will occasionally exceed 90 degrees• Must be able to continuously climb and descend stairs safely (applies to sites with stairs)• Must be able to work on a secure mezzanine at a height of up to 40 feet (applies to buildings with mezzanines)</description>
      <location>CA, AB, Calgary</location>
      <category>Fulfillment &amp; Operations Management</category>
      <job_id>986891</job_id>
      <company_name>AMZN CAN Fulfillment Svcs, ULC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>78f0732c511fb6cb1e31b68a90d2df41</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986888/area-manager-delivery-operations</job_url>
      <title>Area Manager, Delivery Operations</title>
      <description>Do you want to work hard, have fun and make history? If you do, then Amazon could be the right career choice for you. Our logistics teams are changing the way we interact with customers around the globe every single day and solving some of the biggest logistical challenges facing not just Amazon, but also the entire industry.Amazon’s transportation teams work to ensure the delivery of packages for customers around the world. On its busiest day, Cyber Monday, Amazon customers around the world have ordered more than 400 items per second and the transportation teams play a critical role ensuring packages make it to customers’ doors on-time and in great condition. Whether it is an item large or small, we find solutions to make sure we are delivering on our promise for customers.We are looking for a Driver Resource Manager, Logistics who will be responsible for driver success and maintaining a positive driver experience.Key Job Duties· Cultivate and sustain a positive culture, quality performance, safe environment, and a positive, professional driver experience· Subject matter expert for all DA and DSP process areas in the station (Load Out, OnRoad Execution, RTS)· Manage two direct reports responsible for DA training processes and on road audit mechanisms for DAs· Participate in negotiations for DSP dispute resolution, specifically approving payment, determining payment adjustments where appropriate, and managing the DSP invoice process· Conduct weekly performance meetings with DSP owners to develop and ensure adherence to action plans that meet business objectives and to facilitate monthly round tables for owner feedback· Drive continuous cost and process improvement programs while maintaining positive working relationships with DSPs and operations leadership·Partner with regional Fleet Management leadership to validate and confirm vehicle demand during peaks and ramps· Responsible for DSP Compliance to the Fleet Management Program· Lead daily SUMs with the DA population prior to load out to drive quality and engagement· Determine DA scheduling strategy through optimization of delivery route assignment· Oversee response to customer/TOC escalations· Monitor Driver staffing and fleet pipeline to ensure sufficient capacityAdditional Job Elements· Must be able to do the following with or without reasonable accommodation:· Lift up to 70 pounds· Frequently push, pull, squat, bend, and reach· Stand/walk for up to 12 hours· Push and pull wheeled dollies loaded with products up to 100 pounds· Engage in full manual dexterity in both hands and wrists· Work in an environment where the noise level varies and can be loud· Work in an environment where the temperature may vary between 60 and 90 degrees, occasionally exceeding 90 degrees· Continuously climb and descend stairs safely· Must be able to work flexible schedules/shifts/areas, including weekends, nights, and holidays</description>
      <location>CA, AB, Calgary</location>
      <category>Fulfillment &amp; Operations Management</category>
      <job_id>986888</job_id>
      <company_name>AMZN CAN Fulfillment Svcs, ULC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>b4385894d48d5041a92d8b7f4432e2f6</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986886/area-manager-logistics</job_url>
      <title>Area Manager, Logistics</title>
      <description>Do you want to work hard, have fun and make history? If you do, then Amazon could be the right career choice for you. Our logistics teams are changing the way we interact with customers around the globe every single day and solving some of the biggest logistical challenges facing not just Amazon, but also the entire industry.Amazon’s transportation teams work to ensure the delivery of packages for customers around the world. On its busiest day, Cyber Monday, Amazon customers around the world have ordered more than 400 items per second and the transportation teams play a critical role ensuring packages make it to customers’ doors on-time and in great condition. Whether it is an item large or small, we find solutions to make sure we are delivering on our promise for customers.Our Area Managers are responsible for management and supervision over the day-to-day operations of delivery stations in the Amazon network, including inbound, outbound, and sortation operations. Area Managers actively engage with site and regional operations leadership to develop and implement new operational improvements and new services. We expect our managers to continually identify ways to improve our operations.Key Job Duties· Act as second-in-command to Station Manager in managing to achieve station safety, quality, productivity and CE performance and to include interviewing, hiring, promotions, discipline, and terminations of employment· Responsible for managing associates to achieve operational metrics for areas of responsibility· Managing to meet expectations regarding Standard Work, Gemba, reporting and root cause defects· Conduct daily and weekly performance meetings· Oversee response to customer/TOC escalations· Assess and develop future production and labor plans· Interact with all support teams (LP, quality, safety, HR etc.) to develop plans to meet business objectives· Analyze and oversight of scheduling and staffing requirements for area of responsibility· Volume planning/contingency planning· Subject matter expert for all process areas in the station (Sort, OnRoad, RTS)· Ensuring process compliance and reporting for areas of responsibility (LP, Safety, Quality, HR)· Support team interaction and escalation for area of responsibility· Develop an environment that drives performance while maintaining safe environment and ensure timely reporting· Point of contact for safety/security issues that occur on site, incident commander in event of an issue· Day-to-day management/supervision, including coverage and scheduling of L4 Shift Managers· Oversight and participation in ensuring appropriate performance management for Amazon L1-L3 associates (does not apply to temporary associates)· Occasional work in direct process path (if needed)· Vacation coverage for Station Manager (if needed)Additional Job Elements:· Must be able to lift up to 49 pounds with or without reasonable accommodation· Must be willing and able to frequently push, pull, squat, bend, and reach· Must be able to stand/walk for up to 10-12 hours· Must be able to work in an environment where the noise level varies and can be loud· Must be able to work in an environment where the temperature may vary between 60 and 90 degrees, and will occasionally exceed 90 degrees· Must be able to continuously climb and descend stairs safely (applies to sites with stairs)· Must be able to work on a secure mezzanine at a height of up to 40 feet (applies to buildings with mezzanines)</description>
      <location>CA, AB, Calgary</location>
      <category>Fulfillment &amp; Operations Management</category>
      <job_id>986886</job_id>
      <company_name>AMZN CAN Fulfillment Svcs, ULC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>5da2b02eca26bcc5deae570c27938b71</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986878/data-engineer-global-exports</job_url>
      <title>Data Engineer, Global Exports</title>
      <description>Amazon Global Logistics (AGL) supports Amazon’s strategic vision by bringing worldwide cross-border product selection at the lowest price to our customers and helping sellers and vendors (manufacturers, distributors and brand owners) navigate international trade and logistics. We design and build products and programs with a focus on customer, seller, and vendor experience, and global scalability. We’re looking for exceptional leaders to join our team.AGL works directly with logistics cross-border carriers and partner with several stakeholder teams to constantly improve the international delivery experience. AGL Exports Business Intelligence team is seeking a highly skilled and motivated Data Engineer to join our team in Seattle. The AGL Exports business is growing rapidly and the data required to support critical business decisions in this space is provided by the AGL Business Intelligence team. Our ideal candidate is someone who is always learning and improving as the business grows and the relevant technologies continue to evolve. If you enjoy innovating, thinking big and want to contribute directly to the success of an industry changing business, you may be a prime candidate for this position.CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:· Contribute to the architecture, design and implementation of next generation BI solutions – including streaming data applications.· Manage AWS resources including EC2, RDS, Redshift, Kinesis, EMR, Lambda etc.· Collaborate with data scientists, BIEs and Business Analysts to deliver high quality data architecture and pipelines.· Interface with other technology teams to extract, transform, and load data from a wide variety of data sources· Continually improve ongoing reporting and analysis processes, automating or simplifying self-service support for customers</description>
      <location>US, WA, Bellevue</location>
      <category>Business Intelligence</category>
      <job_id>986878</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>4d6a792e26850adbcdeb9e1a87f451e0</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986874/research-scientist</job_url>
      <title>Research Scientist</title>
      <description>Want to stop fraudsters and make a direct multi-million dollar impact to Amazon's bottom line? Come join the AWS Fraud Prevention team and help us prevent fraud and abuse on AWS, the largest and fastest growing public cloud provider.Fraudsters are continually looking for new ways to steal from companies doing business online. We invent new techniques to detect and stop these bad actors, leveraging the latest in data mining, predictive modeling, and enforcement. Our team, AWS Fraud Prevention, is a centralized team within AWS that protects all AWS services from fraud and abuse, and ensures the experience of legitimate AWS customers is not negatively impacted by a few bad actors.As a Research Scientist at Amazon, you’ll:· Gather and formulate business problems into technical framework to solve such problems using Machine Learning and Statistical modeling approaches· Analyze and process large amounts of data and build machine learning models to solve specific business problems· Research and implement novel machine learning, AI and statistical approaches.· Establish scalable, efficient, automated processes for large scale data analyses, and model development, validation and implementation· Work closely with software engineering teams to drive model/solution implementations and new feature creation· Develop state-of-the-art machine learning models that are privacy preserving and robust against adversarial attacks</description>
      <location>US, NY, New York</location>
      <category>Research Science</category>
      <job_id>986874</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>1b8936ec121a39e17fce9eec1e244c96</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:15:23 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/986871/senior-engagement-manager-professional-services</job_url>
      <title>Senior Engagement Manager - Professional Services</title>
      <description>At Amazon Web Services (AWS), we’re hiring a technical Engagement Manager to lead AWS consultants, partner, and client teams. Engagement Managers, manage and deliver AWS cloud products and services that enable our customers to realize their business objectives. These professional services engagements focus on the full platform of AWS customer solutions to help our customers and partners remove constraints and accelerate their journey to AWS.AWS Professional Services engage in a wide variety of projects for customers and partners, providing collective AWS customer experience, best practices, and obsessing about strong success for the Customer. Our team collaborates across the entire AWS organization to bring access to product, service, and training teams, to deliver the right solutions and drive feature innovations for our customers across all industries. Engagement Managers help Customers make decisions to meet their technical and business objectives by providing best practices, proactively identifying and closing project gaps.RESPONSIBILITIES AND ABILITIES INCLUDE:EXPERTISE· Collaborate with AWS field sales, pre-sales, training and support teams to seek to understand our customer’s needs, their business, how success is defined, and ensure that we are exceeding expectations in delivery and developing valued solutions.· Experience leveraging formal project management and development methodologies on enterprise level engagements.· Possesses a deep knowledge of project management best practices and how to apply them in an effective yet pragmatic way across large, complex projects.· Understanding of technology principles and services including infrastructure, business applications, data management, security, application platforms and consumer facing technology.SOLUTIONS· Lead individuals, teams or multiple groups and play an active role in analyzing project goals, creating a plan to achieve those goals, and then driving the AWS team members, customer stakeholders/SMEs and potentially other third parties to achieve those goals while understanding the client environment and any limitations to execution.· Actively looks for ways to improve process efficiencies and effectiveness.· Ability to apply strategic thinking and demonstrate understanding of requirements to execute.· Ability to make decisions guided by policies, procedures and business plan with limited guidance.· Business and financial acumen.· Business case development.DELIVERY· Plan, organize, and manage all phases of a project lifecycle to ensure successful delivery. This includes developing and managing project governance plans, project schedules, team goals, defining success criteria, project milestones, and budgets.· Plays an active role in managing project goals and driving teams to achieve customers’ business outcomes by managing issues, risks, decisions, and action items.· Ability to take ownership, work under pressure and meet deadlines on time.· Ability to challenge, recommend and redirect teams as well as manage client expectations during the engagement.· Takes proactive steps to ensure teams meet or exceed customer expectations.· Works effectively in a dynamic environment with changing priorities.· Results-oriented, prioritizes work activities, plans and stays organized in order to meet commitments.COMMUNICATION· Outstanding written and verbal communication skills with team members and audiences of all levels.· Interfaces with various customer and internal AWS stakeholders which consists of senior leadership teams (C-level execs, SVP/VP, Directors) and project level resources such as SMEs.· Plans and oversees the preparation and dissemination of project communications.· Demonstrates the ability to understand the operating styles of others as well as team/client relationships, team dynamics, and adjusts behavior accordingly to succeed. Recognizes environmental or cultural nuances and adapts.· Excellent presentation, communication (oral &amp; written), and relationship building skills, across all levels of management.TEAMING· Proven success in working with teams and executive leadership in a complex, global company environment.· Team player who effectively integrates, motivates and builds relationships with cross-functional team members (local or remote), sponsors, key stakeholders, executives, and other individuals or organizations involved with or affected by the project.· Proven experience working in a matrix environment, managing multiple stakeholders.· Negotiation and conflict resolution capabilities.· Excellent people management skills, including the ability to influence, negotiate and achieve results through others who are not direct reports.This is a customer facing role. You be required to travel to client locations to deliver professional services when needed.</description>
      <location>US, CA, Irvine</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Technical</category>
      <job_id>986871</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/search.json?base_query=&amp;city=&amp;country=&amp;county=&amp;facets%5B%5D=location&amp;facets%5B%5D=business_category&amp;facets%5B%5D=category&amp;facets%5B%5D=schedule_type_id&amp;facets%5B%5D=employee_class&amp;facets%5B%5D=normalized_location&amp;facets%5B%5D=job_function_id&amp;latitude=&amp;loc_group_id=&amp;loc_query=United+States&amp;longitude=&amp;offset=8340&amp;query_options=&amp;radius=24km&amp;region=&amp;result_limit=10&amp;sort=relevant</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>98427294aa7c987f329ab4fdf4fb0f25</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956579/ad-success-team-manager</job_url>
      <title>Ad Success Team Manager</title>
      <description>Advertising Success Team (AST) is suite of cost-per- click self-serve ad products. AST supports ad products that include Product Ads and Sponsored Products (SP) and both are key components in the advertising program at Amazon.Working with advertisers, you will be responsible for optimization and providing guided on the various advertising programs. You’ll work with a wide range of businesses to eliminate blockers to their success while driving greater commitment and results.To be successful in this role you’ll need to be well organized, assisting multiple advertisers with different issues at any one time. Technically savvy with an interest in online advertising, your verbal and written communication skills should be excellent, being able to clearly explain issues and the paths to resolution quickly and succinctly to the advertisers. Your commitment to the success of our advertising customers should be strong and you should have a proven record of exceeding on your output goals.Core responsibilities include:• Managing a teams on tasks associated to managed advertiser accounts.• Provides end to end advertiser support for optimization• Leads and motivates the team to deliver on meet business goals. Is accountable to meet business goals for their function.• Ensure removal of any roadblocks that hinder goal achievement with minimal supervision• Works with the team to build business reviews, shares with partner teams, peers, management on a regular basis• Proactively gathers, analyzes, and shares data with management to influence business decisions.• Works with the team to identify and implements solutions and pilots to drive process efficiencies &amp; business goals• Contributes to coaching &amp; developing the team on customer interaction &amp; management:• Ensures usage &amp; updation of CRM tool to capture all customer interactions• Work closely with Partner teams to get all CRM tool related issues resolved• Exhibits &amp; drives a culture of putting customer first with the team• Ensures completion of Customer outreach activity for the available lead set as per the defined contact cadence guideline• Ensures timely response to all escalations• Supports the team in maintaining repository of all work done for customers within their team highlights wins and shares gaps in support with solutions with respective individuals• Should capture the voice of customer and share customer pain points with the management team</description>
      <location>CN, 31, Shanghai</location>
      <category>Sales, Advertising, &amp; Account Management</category>
      <job_id>956579</job_id>
      <company_name>AmazonInfoSrvs(BJ)-Shanghai</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>3380eab60417ebc9c85d78c5e0cce226</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956569/associate-catalog-german</job_url>
      <title>Associate - Catalog, German</title>
      <description>Job Profile – Catalog Associate – Retail Business Services (RBS)Amazon.com operates in a virtual, global eCommerce environment without boundaries, and operates a diverse set of businesses in seven countries, including Retail, third party marketplaces, eCommerce platforms, web services for developers.The RBS group is an integral part of Amazon online product lifecycle and buying operations. The team is designed to ensure Amazon remains competitive in the online retail space with the best price, wide selection and good product information. The team’s primary role is to create and enhance retail selection on the worldwide Amazon online catalog. The tasks handled by this group have a direct impact on customer buying decisions and online user experience.The Catalog Associate is the entry-level role in the RBS organization. In this role, the individual works on one or more critical tasks for a particular retail product category. These tasks include (but are not limited to) populating/procuring content for the product catalogs on the Amazon Web Site, interacting/coordinating with vendors/manufacturers, identifying and correcting errors/complaints, maintaining records of work received and work performed. The individual is expected to perform these tasks by using fair judgment in understanding instructions provided by the Process Lead/Manager.Roles and Responsibilities:· Handle the day-to-day volumes of the assigned tasks and ensure the given SLAs are met per quality standards· Understand and correctly use Amazon’s Retail Systems Platform(RSP) to support vendors and buyers in enhancing the retail selection on Amazon’s online catalog· Maintain records of day-to-day work by updating trackers to reflect work done· If there is a possible default on SLAs or quality, flag the escalation in time to the manager or lead· Interacting and coordinating with vendors/buyers to accurately reflect the Amazon catalog for price, product details and other product-related informationSkills and Competencies Required:· · Excellent written and oral communication skills in English· · Strong business communication skills – ability to communicate with internal/external stakeholders clearly and concisely· · MS Excel proficiency – ability to mine voluminous data for specific detail according to instructions provided· · Strong analytical skills – Ability to do high school level arithmetic· · Familiarity with navigating the internet – research techniques on the internet and finding required information quickly· · For foreign language related positions, certain level of proficiency in foreign languages:  · o French: B1 Level or above  · o German: B1 Level or above  · · Ability to dive deep into a problem, perform ‘Root Cause Analysis’ and identify constraints to recommend a solution – on this, we will test the candidate’s ability to think logically through a given issue, structure their thoughts, identify the problem correctly and then recommend appropriate solutions  · · Ability to deal with ambiguity – use discretion and judgment to take decisions on critical business tasks based on available informationExperience and Qualifications:· · Bachelor’s degree in any discipline – Diploma holders will not be considered· · 1 – 2 years of experience in data-driven business operations processes – BPOs, Operations processes where associates are required to handle large volume of data as part of their daily tasks and take decisions based on analysis of such data· · Experience working on process improvement processes like Six Sigma, Kaizen etc. is a plus</description>
      <location>IN, TN, Chennai</location>
      <category>Editorial, Writing, &amp; Content Management</category>
      <job_id>956569</job_id>
      <company_name>ADCI - Tamil Nadu</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>5c376060d06977df7825cc49141c308b</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956568/sr-business-development-manager-aws-high-performance-computing</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Business Development Manager – AWS High Performance Computing</title>
      <description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the pioneer and recognized leader in Cloud Computing. Amazon web services provide a platform for IT infrastructure in-the-cloud that is used by hundreds of thousands of developers and businesses around the world. These customers range from start-ups to leading web companies to Global 500 companies in financial services, pharmaceuticals, and technology. An important function within the AWS organization is Platform Business Development, which is a global function centered around market development for new web services and market expansion for existing web services.AWS is seeking a Sr. Business Development Manager (BDM) to support High-Performance Computing (HPC) business. The BDM will be responsible for helping defining, building and deploying effective and targeted programs to accelerate broad based business development activities for HPC workloads on AWS. The BDM will facilitate the enablement of business development and solution architecture with specific customer centric value propositions and will directly interface with the HPC product management and development teams regarding customer and partner requirements for next gen R&amp;D and other resource intensive workloads. HPC workloads include areas like 2D and 3D rendering for media and entertainment, genomics and proteomics analysis for life sciences and healthcare, oil and gas reservoir simulation for energy exploration, molecular modeling, computational chemistry, aerospace, automotive, semiconductor design, financial computing, fluid dynamics, electromagnetic simulations and complex materials analysis.The BDM will work closely with AWS business development, marketing and partner teams to position the AWS platform for customers and partners, and provide guidance on the value proposition and benefit those customers and partners can achieve with AWS services, platforms, frameworks and infrastructure. In addition, the BDM will help define and drive a process that the organization will follow to accelerate business development and partner-management engagement for related customer and partner opportunities. The BDM will synthesize data and information gathered from these engagements into succinct findings, derive key insights, and persuasively communicate findings and perspectives to product and business development teams, including senior management.The BDM will work with business development and solution architect teams to help track, prioritize and close customer engagements that would benefit from running on AWS EC2 instances, and collaborate and coordinate cross-functional teams around these engagements where appropriate.The ideal candidate will possess a business and IT background that enables them to drive a project and interact at the highest levels of large Enterprises and Enterprise partners. The candidate will have the technical depth and business experience to easily communicate the benefits of machine learning and deep learning services, platforms and frameworks in the AWS cloud to IT architects, engineering teams, and C-Level executives. The ideal candidate will have a demonstrated ability to think strategically and long-term about the needs of complex global businesses. The ideal candidate will also be deeply familiar with complex legacy IT environments, managed enterprise IT infrastructure services, Enterprise applications, and has done market analysis, deal negotiation and construction, business operations, and has a background that enables them to create scalable programs that apply holistic approaches to selling to Enterprises and Enterprise Partners.Roles &amp; Responsibilities:· Help to define, build and deploy enterprise focused business development campaigns around the AWS HPC offering· Help to engage and drive scale at engaging enterprise customers and partners about the AWS HPC value proposition· Exhibits proactive ability and expertise in supporting customer discussions via AWS business development and partner teams· Exhibits HPC expertise and experienced handling business development campaigns with enterprises and enterprise partners· Exhibits expertise and helps to drive field and partner readiness for enterprise customers· Participates in senior level customer meetings to discuss customer’s business issues and explores how the AWS HPC solutions can help address cloud-enabled growth areas· Serves as an evangelist for the HPC platform within AWS and externally· Develops a standard market intelligence framework and dynamic analytic model to be utilized by the AWS Business Development and marketing team· Bring the various stakeholders together to help build collective mindshare in augmenting AWS HPC solutions· Establish ways to measure and track metrics related to adoption of the related AWS solutions, and to make improvements to the approach based on those measurementsPrepare and give business reviews to the senior management team regarding progress and metrics</description>
      <location>UK, London</location>
      <category>Business &amp; Merchant Development</category>
      <job_id>956568</job_id>
      <company_name>AWS EMEA SARL (UK Branch)</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>6771c756255909d81553efd7dd083f4e</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956565/software-development-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer</title>
      <description>Interested in working on IoT products, AWS cloud services, edge computing, getting a taste of deep learning technology for computer vision? This opportunity has it all!As a Software Development Engineer on the AWS AI team, you will build scalable and robust cloud services and APIs that will bring cutting edge deep learning technology to consumer IoT products at Amazon and also enable consumers to manage their IoT devices at scale.Software Engineers at Amazon do so much more than just software development. We are looking for talented and motivated engineers who:· Exhibit excellent judgment· Has relentlessly high standards (is never satisfied with the status quo)· Decide what features to build.· Drive software engineering best practice.· Design distributed and scalable systems.· Test and document the software you develop.</description>
      <location>US, CA, East Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>956565</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>aa9e94c72eb9cd58a4654750208e8353</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956561/brand-development-associate</job_url>
      <title>Brand Development Associate</title>
      <description>About the ProgramEmerging Brands Program team’s mission to build the most effective platform for motivated entrepreneurs to establish &amp; scale consumer direct brands in India, thereby allowing creating a funnel of high quality selection as alternatives to established brands, at the best prices for Amazon’s customers. We achieve this by providing a suite of marketing services and self-service tools that span the entire lifecycle of a Brand, spanning Discovery, Consumer Insights, Selection, Pricing, Fulfillment, and Brand Protection &amp; Exclusive Privileges. First of our solutions for private label brands is Amazon Select (www.amazon.in/launchpad).About the RoleWe are looking for a hands-on, detail oriented and highly motivated sales and account management associate to help drive the program adoption, and brand development value proposition delivery for Amazon Launchpad brands. The ideal candidate will have sales experience, ability to work in an environment with minimal supervision, comfortable working across multiple complex functions and capability to influence external parties. The candidate should be comfortable interfacing with technology systems, training other stakeholders on systems and processes and be able to analyze data and gather actionable conclusions. Operating in a rapidly changing environment will require the candidate to be adept at dealing with ambiguous, new and challenging situations. The candidate will be comfortable in executing repeatable processes.Role and Responsibilities:· Understand products and services offered by Amazon Services and be able to articulate its functions and benefits to external clients/brands.· Identify and acquire valuable sellers and selection for Amazon services.· Own and manage integration of portfolio of sellers and help them become self-reliant through basic training. Focus on brand development and exceeding sales goals of our clientele.· Discovery of strategic business opportunities for our customers through cross function collaboration with category teams, sales teams etc.· Track and monitor performance and sales of key accounts to manage their performance.</description>
      <location>IN, KA, Bangalore</location>
      <category>Business &amp; Merchant Development</category>
      <job_id>956561</job_id>
      <company_name>ASSPL - Karnataka</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>6cf0dfeaf20d2e7f81ac8cf6f3dff00f</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956560/software-development-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer</title>
      <description>Interested in working on IoT products, AWS cloud services, edge computing, getting a taste of deep learning technology for computer vision? This opportunity has it all!As a Software Development Engineer on the AWS AI team, you will build scalable and robust cloud services and APIs that will bring cutting edge deep learning technology to consumer IoT products at Amazon and also enable consumers to manage their IoT devices at scale.Software Engineers at Amazon do so much more than just software development. We are looking for talented and motivated engineers who:· Exhibit excellent judgment· Has relentlessly high standards (is never satisfied with the status quo)· Decide what features to build.· Drive software engineering best practice.· Design distributed and scalable systems.· Test and document the software you develop.</description>
      <location>US, CA, East Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>956560</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>722bf1c60972ef0f435b97cc0d11e4ea</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956559/software-development-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer</title>
      <description>Interested in working on IoT products, AWS cloud services, edge computing, getting a taste of deep learning technology for computer vision? This opportunity has it all!As a Software Development Engineer on the AWS AI team, you will build scalable and robust cloud services and APIs that will bring cutting edge deep learning technology to consumer IoT products at Amazon and also enable consumers to manage their IoT devices at scale.Software Engineers at Amazon do so much more than just software development. We are looking for talented and motivated engineers who:· Exhibit excellent judgment· Has relentlessly high standards (is never satisfied with the status quo)· Decide what features to build.· Drive software engineering best practice.· Design distributed and scalable systems.· Test and document the software you develop.</description>
      <location>US, CA, East Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>956559</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>debbfc6ed87fdaae877e6a40f77d67ac</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956551/associate-marketing-manager</job_url>
      <title>Associate Marketing Manager</title>
      <description>Are you customer obsessed, smart and analytical, strategic yet execution focused, entrepreneurial, and passionate about e-Commerce? Do you want to be a part of one of the fastest growing and most innovative e-commerce businesses? Are you interested in working in a high impact role? If yes, this opportunity will appeal to you. Come join our Marketing team and help define the course of the Amazon business.Amazon's vision is to enable customers globally to find, discover, and buy anything online. The company’s sales figure was at $48 billion in 2011 and is expected to grow by more than 25% this year. Amazon.com operates along with its affiliate websites, across the globe, delighting millions of customers every day.We are looking for a smart, metrics and results-oriented Site Merchandiser who will be instrumental in improving customer experience and growing our business. The site merchandiser will be responsible for ensuring the best customer experience in one or more product line(s). He/she will plan, coordinate, and create emails and pages across the site; create and analyses metrics dashboards following traffic, click through, conversion, adoption and other web metrics. He/she will report on performance and action plans to the management team; will propose, plan and execute new features and projects, partnering with business and technical teams to achieve goals. He/she will help to drive feature launches and site improvements to completion by coordinating with project managers, developers, designers, and peers across the organization.What will your responsibilities include?§ Handling design, tracking, analytics, merchandising and owning complete responsibility for all campaigns related to consumer financing on Amazon.in like EMI, Insurance &amp; more.§ Tracking and analyzing customer needs based on customer behavior including searching, browsing and purchasing§ Formulating and executing the marketing plan. This includes email and push programs, new product launches, cross-category placements, developing and executing Amazon site wide events etc.§ Designing and executing successful online customer experiences§ Identifying problems and opportunities and responding accordingly, engaging cross functional teams where necessary§ Developing and managing SEO initiatives, free search improvement projects, online ads, social media campaigns and new traffic-driving content strategies§ Analyzing and sharing relevant metrics and best practices from the executed initiatives across the organization§ Developing, testing and analyzing new tactics to increase conversion rates and sharing them within the organization</description>
      <location>IN, KA, Bangalore</location>
      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
      <job_id>956551</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Pay(India) Private Lmtd</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>6d71da83e08875d82e941ee5b37cc63b</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956550/senior-product-manager-amazon-pay-rewards</job_url>
      <title>Senior Product Manager, Amazon Pay Rewards</title>
      <description>Senior Product Manager – Amazon Pay RewardsAmazon Pay's vision is to be the most trusted, accessible, frictionless and ubiquitous payments system, preferred by millions of customers to pay in a wide range of use cases and contexts. As part of this, we are embarking on building a merchant network that would provide our customer more avenues to experience our world class products and contribute towards making India a cashless economy. These merchants will be able to showcase their Ads or Product offers to Amazon.in customers and get additional visibility via the Amazon Pay merchant affiliate program.We are looking for a Product Leader who drive the roadmap for discovery, conversion and buying experience of these offers on the Amazon. Incorporation of amplified visibility for merchants who have signed up for the Amazon pay affiliate programs across the various discovery paradigms with the necessary guardrails to provide a top notch customer experience is also an important part of this role. The leader donning the role should have a good understanding of Search relevance, personalized recommendations, affinity based models used in Ad recommendations, Ad or Product offer quality, Metrics &amp; instrumentation. S/he will have a direct and visible impact on the long term success of the program. This role would have direct exposure to senior leaders within Amazon. The role will start as an individual contributor role based in Bangalore and will report to the Product Leader for Rewards, Amazon Pay.The ideal candidate will:· Have an entrepreneurial spirit with strong background in online product, payments and a track record of creating innovative internet solutions.· Be comfortable with “hands-on” day-to-day problem solving, implementing quick and effective action plans to meet short term priorities. Equally comfortable in generating a 3-year strategic vision and a weekly sales report.· Have proven analytical skills and an ability to manage a program “by the numbers”. Must be metrics-driven.· Have excellent written and oral communication and presentation skills and the ability to express thoughts logically and succinctly. Demonstrated active listening skills, highly consultative and solutions-oriented. Proven ability to influence others.</description>
      <location>IN, KA, Bangalore</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Non-Tech</category>
      <job_id>956550</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Pay(India) Private Lmtd</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>cdd655636aa6515bd582a93ab303639b</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:36 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/956549/senior-technical-account-manager-come-build-with-us</job_url>
      <title>Senior Technical Account Manager - Come Build with Us</title>
      <description>Do you have a technical background and looking for a flexible role where you can help businesses scale in the cloud?About UsAt Amazon, our vision is to be earth’s most customer-centric company. In 2006, we launched Amazon Web Services, giving customers access to the same cloud technology we built to serve millions of shoppers on Amazon.com. Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a secure cloud services platform, offering computing power, database storage, content delivery, and other functionality to help millions of businesses scale and grow.The RoleAs a trusted advisor you’ll have a direct impact in helping our customers gain the most value from cloud technology. You’ll craft and execute strategies to drive our customers’ adoption and use of AWS services. Our Technical Account Managers (TAMs) partner with some of the most iconic businesses in the country. These range from rising startups building their business from scratch through to large enterprises going through significant transformation.You’ll provide advice on architecture, support strategy, project, and launch planning as well as ongoing operational issues. In this senior role, you will have an opportunity to impact organization wide processes and roadmaps, directly influencing how customers are use AWS in the long term.Watch a short video about life in our Enterprise Support team here https://bit.ly/2kiEESEResponsibilities include:-· Enable C-suite executives to embrace agility and deliver high impact transformation· Lead and sponsor customer enablement programs that uplift our customer's capabilities· Communicate transformational concepts to executive decision makers· Own and define the technical strategy including establishing metrics, governance forums etc.· Build solutions, provide technical guidance and advocate for the customer· Ensure AWS environments remain operationally healthy whilst reducing cost and complexity· Foster trusting relationships with customers, understanding their business needs and technical challenges· Using your technical acumen and customer obsession, you’ll drive technical discussions with senior leadership regarding incidents, trade-offs, and risk management· Collaborate with AWS Solutions Architects, Business Developers, Professional Services Consultants, and Sales Account Managers· Being part of a wider Enterprise Support team you’ll provide post-sales, consultative expertise· With a bias for action, you'll proactively find opportunities for customers to gain additional value from AWSLonger term, you will have the chance to further develop your technical, consulting and leadership skills as we continue to grow the team. You’ll develop your knowledge of AWS services, have the opportunity to gain further certifications as well as receive mentorship.Our TAMs work autonomously with a focus on customer outcomes. You’ll spend time between the office and customer sites as well as have the opportunity to work from home.CultureAt Amazon Web Services, we don't mind being called "peculiar." We have our own way of doing things. We're obsessed with customers, we see beauty in simplifying the complex, and we're comfortable with being misunderstood. That might sound unorthodox, but our unusual approach and our culture - focused on removing obstacles so builders can build - are part of why our people enjoy working in AWS.We’re passionate about supporting the needs of our people and their family members. Benefits include Medical Cover, Employee Assistance Programs and Global Mobility opportunities.</description>
      <location>AU, ACT, Canberra</location>
      <category>Solutions Architect</category>
      <job_id>956549</job_id>
      <company_name>AWS Australia Pty Ltd</company_name>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/search.json?base_query=&amp;city=&amp;country=&amp;county=&amp;facets%5B%5D=location&amp;facets%5B%5D=business_category&amp;facets%5B%5D=category&amp;facets%5B%5D=schedule_type_id&amp;facets%5B%5D=employee_class&amp;facets%5B%5D=normalized_location&amp;facets%5B%5D=job_function_id&amp;latitude=&amp;loc_group_id=&amp;loc_query=United+States&amp;longitude=&amp;offset=7110&amp;query_options=&amp;radius=24km&amp;region=&amp;result_limit=10&amp;sort=relevant</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>6b745f0dfdfb8aba7d584d12bc712643</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960293/software-development-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer</title>
      <description>Prime Video is changing the way millions of customers interact with video content. The Prime Video team delivers high-quality instant video to Amazon customers through subscriptions (Amazon Prime) as well as purchases and rentals. Amazon believes so deeply in the mission of Video that we've launched our own studio to create original and exclusive content. Every day we face the challenges of a fast paced market and expanding technology set. As a member of the Video team, you will spend your time as a hands-on engineer and a technical leader. You will play a key role in building software products and features from the ground up. You will use a wide range of technologies, programming languages and systems. Your responsibilities will include all aspects of software development. You will have the freedom and encouragement to explore your own ideas and the reward of seeing your contributions benefit millions of Amazon.com customers worldwide.The QuEST (Quality Excellence Services and Tools) team improve Quality Processes at scale; we are leading a fundamental change in how teams with complex dependency chains design, build and validate their software. Our software helps teams to automate and measure their quality practices, making it faster than ever to get a high confidence data driven quality signal as soon as they write code.You will be focused on key projects that will fundamentally change the way in which teams deploy and test their software, with the scope to be able to impact each and every team in Prime Video, improving their software quality to the benefit of Amazon's customers. You will work closely with a wide array of teams, understanding how teams work now and how we can have maximum impact and improve the toolsets for teams, or create the toolsets they are missing. You will work with the latest AWS technologies, to build new capabilities, such as the use of ML techniques to identify trends, patterns, and anomalies in test data to help teams improve their quality practices.</description>
      <location>UK, London</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>960293</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Dev Centre (London) Ltd</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>27d156dd88e7593868d31d148aa30cb2</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960291/360-creative-director-amazon-prime-video-original-series</job_url>
      <title>360 Creative Director – Amazon Prime Video: Original Series</title>
      <description>Amazon Studios is seeking creative, talented and passionate Creative Director to create innovative, stunning and effective marketing experiences that drive viewership of the original programming that we distribute through Amazon Prime Video. The ideal candidate will combine creative inspiration with the ability to create thoughtful, groundbreaking, inspirational creative that will connect with customers across all channels.Sr. Creative Directors own the following for primary, secondary, and portfolio seriesCreative Thinking· Personally ideate and develop innovative, stunning and effective 360° marketing experiences that tell stories, communicate benefits, and drive viewership of our highest priority original programming that we distribute through Amazon Prime Video· Come up with a creative vision and direction that is contagious for others to buy into for our most important and highest impact projects and bring that vision to fruition as part of 360° campaigns executed via internal and external partners.· Use programs such as Adobe CS and Microsoft Office to create artifacts such as creative briefs, presentation decks, sketches, and comps to communicate concepts and bring ideas to life· Articulate and sell creative concepts to peers, senior management and Executive Producers· Solve for business, customer, and stakeholder requirements while building creative that is unique, stunning and effective· Proactively ideate and define creative deliverables across channels that help drive marketing objectivesCreative Execution· Elevate the creative output of any internal partner or agency/production company vendor to ensure that all marketing assets meet a high level of creativity, innovation and brand association on time and within budget· Obtain and allocate internal/external resources to achieve strategic and operating goals· Manages highly visible and complex projects that have wide impact across the business and/or spans across multiple teams or platforms· Effectively direct and manage the development of all creative assets for marketing materials including key art and trailers; video, digital, social media, print, merchandising and other assets for a combination of shows with a large degree of autonomy, communicating needs and trade-offs if schedule is at risk· Forecast resourcing needs and work with key stakeholders to drive a schedule for projects while prioritizing and using resources effectively· Approve creative and manage blockers or obstacles in the process.· Identify and implement appropriate process and level of effort to meet business needs· Facilitate meetings with all levels of management both internal and external· Allocate, manage and track budgets for creative asset development· Lead the execution of key campaign creative assets within budget and on-time· Build strategic relationships with internal and external stakeholders, and communicate and collaborate effectively across teams and functions to achieve high-level outcomes, with lower costs· Work with cross functional leaders to ensure cohesion of process and brand across internal and external stakeholders· Proactively work to solve problems and communicate to senior management, and actively seek clarification when there is ambiguityLeadership· Coaches and mentors junior staff· Communicate with key stakeholders internally (Pods, Marketing Group, Studios and PV organization, Amazon) and externally (partner agencies) in a spirit of collaboration, building strong relationships with stakeholders, communicating and collaborating effectively, articulating complex issues/problems in an effective manner· Work with senior leadership to create policies and procedures, best practices that impact the broader departmentAbout Amazon StudiosAmazon Studios launched in 2010 as a new way to develop feature films and episodic series—one that’s open to great ideas from creators and audiences around the world. Amazon Studios Original Content is available to Prime members and is known for bringing customers the Golden Globe-winning and Emmy-winning series The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel, Fleebag, Transparent, Goliath, Mozart in the Jungle and The Man in the High Castle, along with original hits like Jack Ryan, The Boys, Carnival Row, The Grand Tour, Sneaky Pete, Bosch, Catastrophe and All or Nothing. Prime members also have access to a collection of Amazon Original series for kids such as Wishenpoof, Stinky &amp; Dirty, Just Add Magic, Kicks, Lost In Oz and American Girl Specials, and multi-Emmy Award-winning Tumble Leaf.Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer – Minority / Female / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation.</description>
      <location>US, CA, Culver City</location>
      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
      <job_id>960291</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>05e7d8799fb13fb02643b119f40bcd2f</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960282/senior-financial-analyst-supply-chain-optimization-technologies</job_url>
      <title>Senior Financial Analyst - Supply Chain Optimization Technologies</title>
      <description>Amazon is a fast paced, dynamic, technology company based in Seattle. The company continues to grow revenue at double digits, executing a simple strategy: “to be earth’s most customer-centric company; to build a place where people can come to find and discover anything they might want to buy online.” Amazon operates the most complex retail networks in the world, delivering billions of packages to hundreds of millions of homes and businesses annually. The Supply Chain Optimization Technologies (SCOT) team automates and optimizes decision-making for this network.The Supply Chain Optimization Technologies (SCOT) Finance team is seeking a Senior Financial Analyst (SFA) to support the Automated Inventory Management and Product Availability teams. This role will support a growing business organization responsible for automating the inventory management function, taking over responsibility for day-to-day inventory management operations, audit functions, and owning the key performance indicators used across Amazon to manage inventory and delight customers. This is an opportunity to establish and improve the metrics, mechanisms, and operating parameters that effectively monitor, manage, and report on Amazon’s worldwide inventory position.The SFA will serve as a key business partner providing financial perspective, guidance, and insight on the performance and optimization of a multi-billion dollar operations network and Retail inventory position. This role will involve interacting with a cross-functional team including product managers, software engineers, economists, business intelligence engineers, statisticians, Retail business leaders, and supply chain experts to build tools and operational metrics that quantify and explain Amazon’s inventory position across our global network.Specific Responsibilities include:· Identifying and structuring financial support for the WW Automated Inventory Management and Product Availability function.· Support the execution of key financial targets and metrics through the development and implementation of proactive dashboards, measurements and variance analyses.· Partnering with business teams to calculate and understand financial trade-offs and implications of key inventory management and product availability metrics· Ensure appropriate financial controls are being applied by our automated inventory management systems· Coordinate and draft narratives for Operating Plans, Business Reviews and other initiatives· Build and maintain a high level of knowledge across all business areas by staying current on initiatives, challenges, and opportunities across SCOT and the Retail business that impact inventory management· Serve as the liaison between the Retail Finance and Operations Finance teams, helping drive transparency in our inventory management systems and associated outputs.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Finance &amp; Accounting</category>
      <job_id>960282</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>d5617e1f5e5f7b6ce3f510c3a5bc4bfe</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960278/senior-product-manager</job_url>
      <title>Senior Product Manager</title>
      <description>Does the opportunity to influence how customers discover products excite you? Do you have experience identifying customer pain points in the shopping experience and implementing scalable solutions to resolve root cause defects? If you answered yes to both, we have an exciting role for you. We are looking for a Sr. Product Manager to join Hardlines Retail Operations and Initiatives responsible for improving product discoverability.From Day 1, Sr. Product Managers are given ownership of large scale products, the autonomy to think strategically and make data driven decisions, and the ability to drive significant impact to the customer experience and the business. A senior product manager role with the Retail Operations &amp; Initiatives team provides the unique opportunity to come up with new innovative ideas, launch new initiatives, and make a large impact at scale across numerous product categories. You will shape products and lead solutions while being pushed to grow into a senior leader who thinks big, acts globally, and delivers for customers.At Amazon, we continue to add selection that delights our customers and fulfills their shopping needs. As the Sr. Product Manager for discoverability, you will develop the vision, roadmap, and success criteria for new features designed to help customers find products that deliver the best CX. To improve product discoverability, you will identify features to improve how customers discover products they want/need through improvements in browse experience, search and product imaging. You'll use various technologies to test and optimize UX, engagement, and conversion. Further, you will work with worldwide tech partners and influence significant decisions and stakeholders across the company.A successful Sr. Product Manager will be able to understand, prioritize, and manage CX and financial levers as well as technical concepts. The candidate will have excellent product and program management skills, communication proficiency, and motivation to deliver results in a fast-paced environment. Candidates should demonstrate a passion for working on behalf of customers, have a track record of timely delivery of large scale projects, and have the ability to operate independently. Judgment, influence, and creativity are all essential.#ReinventRetail</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Non-Tech</category>
      <job_id>960278</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>32b076b7bf0518ad2d511b784a138923</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960277/open-source-marketing-coordinator</job_url>
      <title>Open Source Marketing Coordinator</title>
      <description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) is seeking an exceptionally bright, multitasking and self-motivated marketing coordinator to support the AWS Open Source Marketing Team. This role requires superior attention to detail, the ability to meet tight deadlines, and great organizational skills. The successful candidate will possess the ability to complete a high volume of complex tasks and projects quickly with little to no guidance and react with appropriate urgency to situations that require a quick turnaround.The most successful candidate must possess a relentless bias for action, the ability to effectively communicate at all levels, is extremely detail oriented and very organized. This position will work closely with teams across the Amazon Web Services marketing. You must have the ability to quickly learn organizational structure, team objectives and adapt to Amazon values and vision. Additionally, the ideal candidate must be able to work successfully in a team environment, building effective working relationships inside and outside of the group, while keeping abreast of general business objectives, policies, standards, procedures and related information in order to maintain a comprehensive awareness of the organization. A high level of integrity and discretion in handling confidential information, and professionalism in dealing with senior professionals inside and outside the company is important.We expect this impactful person to:· Proactively coordinate and engage with the team leadership in planning and organizing events, activities, and calendars.· Collaborate and assist on participant recruitment for key internal and external outreach events (hackathons, learning days, meetups, and other less formal events)· Management of complex calendar and scheduling requirements to ensure highly complex meetings synchronize across all parties and execute smoothly· Tracking and helping drive completion of key team deliverables and following up on outstanding items· Manage the team communications calendar· Procure and manage inventory for promotional assets for customer/community rewards· Live tweet and promote AWS via social media at key events· Collect data from events and run email campaigns to gather Open Source NPS results.· Manage internal training resources, curating content and driving teams to produce/update material related to field and partner enablement.· Create a repository of open source related presentations, abstracts, and spokespeople to support 3P events, EBCs, and smaller meetups/hackathons.· Have fun at work and help others do the same</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
      <job_id>960277</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>36f944cbb7fca28f0e75cf585ce933c2</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960271/global-sales-account-representative</job_url>
      <title>Global Sales Account Representative</title>
      <description>Amazon Global Selling is seeking a dynamic and motivated Account Executive who can prospect and facilitate the international expansion of US Based Selling Partners to Amazon European marketplaces. As an organization, Amazon Global Selling is highly influential by coordinating across sales organizations globally, Product teams, and Category teams.This role will focus on building win-win relationships with Selling Partners to increase engagement and adoption of growth-driving programs. Specifically, this person will be responsible for not only creating and managing their sales pipeline, but taking ownership in driving sales related projects, and owning goals and reporting on particular categories or territory responsibilities. This person will directly interface with executive level contacts of prospective Selling Partners to facilitate all stages of a sale. The best candidate will drive and create proposals, business cases, and responses to customers' business requirements and take a consultative sales approach.Primary Responsibilities:· Work with a sense of urgency to drive and deliver sales goals while maintaining a high quality of work· Operate with a continuous motor to identify, recruit and motivate potential Selling Partners to expand globally· Work with Sellers to achieve data quality standards and become an expert in using internal tools to achieve results· Drive business reviews with sellers and do analysis to understand sales trends and drivers and develop recommendations on how to grow the business· Develop a thorough understanding of the specific market segments, seasonality and global business trends/events· Implement account management best practices and SOPs into the business development framework· Partner with other Amazon teams including Category Management (CMMs), Program Development, and other Global Selling teams to align programs and initiatives to drive growth in existing seller baseScope of Work and Time Distribution:· 40% - New Program recruiting (Phone, E-mail)· 40% - Post-Launch Account Management to increase Seller’s selection and revenue· 10% - Projects· 5% - Documentation· 5% - Meetings/Training</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Sales, Advertising, &amp; Account Management</category>
      <job_id>960271</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Services LLC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>5ac7169e36334410e59896c37c76a77f</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960270/sr-operations-program-manager</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Operations Program Manager</title>
      <description>JP Global Specialty Fulfillment (GSF) comprises is looking for a Sr. Operations Program Manager to launch a new print-on-demand production center facility and then drive strategic initiatives to scale Operations post launch.As a Sr. Operations Program Manager, you will first define, execute, and deliver against a roadmap to ensure we select, prepare, and deliver a top-tier print-on-demand production center to support the new business.You will work internally across multiple functions spanning Amazon.co.jp and Amazon.com, including Ops Engineering &amp; Design, Ops Finance, Category Leadership, Accounting, Tax, Legal, and business leadership at Amazon HQ in Seattle. After ensuring a successful production center facility launch, you’ll develop metrics and goals to drive productivity improvements and cost reductions and regularly collaborate with the Europe and US Operations teams to ensure consistent R&amp;D, compliance, and process standards across the global organization.* Although this position is centered on Meguro work, there is a possibility of a flexible work system for business trips and on-site support.アマゾンジャパンのグローバルスペシャリティフルフィルメント本部 オペレーション開発部ではお客様の更なる利便性向上を図るべく、様々なオペレーション開発、新機能導入、新サービス立上げをリードするプログラムマネージャーを求めています。本ポジションは、お客様、プロダクションセンター、販売サイド、ファイナンス、海外エンジニアリングチーム、海外R&amp;Dチームなどの関係者を結ぶ架け橋として機能し、グローバルスペシャリティフルフィルメントオペレーションの中枢として、プリントオンデマンドサービスプロダクションセンターの立ち上げや品質基準の策定、立ち上げ後の標準化、最適化、監査、生産性・品質の向上ならびにサービス拡大を推進することに責任を持ちます。Amazonの成長と共に自分自身も成長させようと考えていらっしゃる、やる気のある方を募集しております。※このポジションは目黒勤務中心ですが、出張や現場対応でフレキシブルな勤務体系になる可能性があります。Key Responsibilities· Defining, executing, coordinating, communicating, and delivering against a project roadmap to effectively launch the print-on-demand production center facility in Japan· Overseeing on-site installation and qualification of all JP equipment· Regularly collaborating with US and EU Amazon Operations Support, Supply Chain, and R&amp;D teams to ensure JP Amazon standards are consistent with those of the US and EU Amazon businesses· Developing and driving daily operations metrics to meet or exceed productivity, efficiency, and cost reduction goals· Defining and implementing manufacturing quality standards· Auditing quality standards compliance· Managing Author/Customer complaints· Driving IT Amazon system improvements· Proactively helping hire the Amazon production center leadership team that includes the site leader, production managers, area managers and other production center team members.Key Responsibilities· プロジェクトのロードマップに沿って、様々な仕様・基準の策定、プロジェクトの実行・コントロール、ステークホルダーとのコミュニケーションを円滑に実施し、効率的にプリントオンデマンドサービスの立ち上げをリード並びにサポートする· 日本への機器導入、管理運営方法の構築を担う· US、EUのオペレーション、サプライチェーン、R&amp;Dチームと定期的にコミュニケーションをとり、日本のオペレーションがグローバル標準に沿うよう管理する· メトリクス（KPI）を構築し、生産性、効率、コスト削減のゴール達成をドライブする· 生産品質基準の定義・導入を実施する· 生産品質基準に適合しているかの監査を実施する· お客様、プログラム参加者からのクレームに対処する· ITシステムの改善をドライブする· プロダクションセンターのリーダー、マネージャー、チームメンバーの採用に協力する【More Information】■勤務地（目黒）紹介https://www.amazon.co.jp/b?node=5589794051■職種(プロジェクトマネジメント)紹介https://www.amazon.co.jp/b?node=5609904051</description>
      <location>JP, 13, Meguro</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Non-Tech</category>
      <job_id>960270</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Japan G.K.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>bf33911eb74a6bfc2e5ed54ad68c49b1</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960269/global-sales-account-representative</job_url>
      <title>Global Sales Account Representative</title>
      <description>Amazon Global Selling is seeking a dynamic and motivated Account Executive who can prospect and facilitate the international expansion of US Based Selling Partners to Amazon European marketplaces. As an organization, Amazon Global Selling is highly influential by coordinating across sales organizations globally, Product teams, and Category teams.This role will focus on building win-win relationships with Selling Partners to increase engagement and adoption of growth-driving programs. Specifically, this person will be responsible for not only creating and managing their sales pipeline, but taking ownership in driving sales related projects, and owning goals and reporting on particular categories or territory responsibilities. This person will directly interface with executive level contacts of prospective Selling Partners to facilitate all stages of a sale. The best candidate will drive and create proposals, business cases, and responses to customers' business requirements and take a consultative sales approach.Primary Responsibilities:· Work with a sense of urgency to drive and deliver sales goals while maintaining a high quality of work· Operate with a continuous motor to identify, recruit and motivate potential Selling Partners to expand globally· Work with Sellers to achieve data quality standards and become an expert in using internal tools to achieve results· Drive business reviews with sellers and do analysis to understand sales trends and drivers and develop recommendations on how to grow the business· Develop a thorough understanding of the specific market segments, seasonality and global business trends/events· Implement account management best practices and SOPs into the business development framework· Partner with other Amazon teams including Category Management (CMMs), Program Development, and other Global Selling teams to align programs and initiatives to drive growth in existing seller baseScope of Work and Time Distribution:· 40% - New Program recruiting (Phone, E-mail)· 40% - Post-Launch Account Management to increase Seller’s selection and revenue· 10% - Projects· 5% - Documentation· 5% - Meetings/Training</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Sales, Advertising, &amp; Account Management</category>
      <job_id>960269</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Services LLC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>a0e9d0200deb0c233d657320b2559558</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960251/software-development-engineer-aws-ai</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer – AWS AI</title>
      <description>Come and be part of the Amazon AI Labs team and work on cutting edge machine learning algorithms for the Amazon SageMaker platform!With Machine Learning, businesses now ask our machines to do more than repetitive, strictly-defined tasks. We are taking it one step further and have begun to ask them to not only learn on their own but to also interpret data and report to the customer before they even knew they needed it. It's a step in history for you to be a part of. You will be building a platform that incorporates best practices and runs advanced algorithms at production scale and reliability.We are a team of data scientists and engineers who experiment, research, and turn machine/deep learning and AI research into great products for our customers.You will work in a fast-paced environment and do everything from determining priorities, designing features, re-architecting as necessary, automating testing, and mentoring others. The best candidates show true end-to-end ownership. In this role, you will be responsible for building algorithms, tooling, frameworks, and operational processes using technologies like MxNet, Python, C++, CUDA, Docker, etc.Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer – Minority / Female / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation</description>
      <location>US, NY, New York</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>960251</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>09742e966fa08616bc0fd0ce1dff6824</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:13:07 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/960243/senior-financial-analyst-global-it</job_url>
      <title>Senior Financial Analyst, Global IT</title>
      <description>Join the Amazon Web Services (AWS) Finance team! We are looking for entrepreneurial, analytical, creative, flexible leaders to help us redefine the IT industry. If you want to join a fast-paced, innovative team that is making history, this is the place for you.AWS is one of Amazon’s fastest growing businesses, servicing millions of customers in more than 190 countries, reshaping the way global enterprises consume information technology and powering developers who are building the next generation of global industry leaders. AWS customers include some of the most innovative startups like Netflix, Pinterest, Airbnb, and Instagram as well as some of the largest global enterprises like Shell International, Unilever, Hitachi, Sharp, Bristol-Myers Squibb, and SamsungAmazon seeks a Senior Financial Analyst to play a key role on our Global IT Finance team. This is an exciting opportunity to be a part of a team that provides IT Services to Amazonians anytime, anywhere, any . device access to business products and services. Job responsibilities include:· Serve as the key finance partner supporting the Global IT team by providing financial support and business insights· Develop financial models and advanced analytical tools that aid in key decision making· Help business leaders understand progress to goals as well as strategic insights to guide overall direction· · Perform ad-hoc analysis as needed and present findings to business leadersHave you had experience in past roles supporting decision making in rapidly evolving environments? Are you a self-starter with strong data gathering and modeling skills, a keen attention to detail, and prior experience working in a fast-paced environment? Are you looking for an exciting role that has regular interaction with various teams across Amazon? Do you have strong interpersonal and communication skills and a desire to collaborate with others? If so, the Global IT Finance team could be the right fit for you!</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Finance &amp; Accounting</category>
      <job_id>960243</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/search.json?base_query=&amp;city=&amp;country=&amp;county=&amp;facets%5B%5D=location&amp;facets%5B%5D=business_category&amp;facets%5B%5D=category&amp;facets%5B%5D=schedule_type_id&amp;facets%5B%5D=employee_class&amp;facets%5B%5D=normalized_location&amp;facets%5B%5D=job_function_id&amp;latitude=&amp;loc_group_id=&amp;loc_query=United+States&amp;longitude=&amp;offset=3070&amp;query_options=&amp;radius=24km&amp;region=&amp;result_limit=10&amp;sort=relevant</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>ebbfe8e0204325a444aac97cb69d85f1</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977773/sr-manufacturing-engineer</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Manufacturing Engineer</title>
      <description>Are you inspired by invention? Is problem solving through teamwork in your DNA? Do you like the idea of seeing how your work impacts the bigger picture? Answer yes to any of these and you’ll fit right in here at Amazon. We are a smart team of doers that work passionately to apply cutting edge advances in robotics and software to solve real-world challenges that will transform our customers’ experiences in ways we can’t even imagine yet.The Amazon Robotics (AR) Operations organization manufactures high-quality robotics and gets the right materials to the right place at the right time to enable our automated solutions. It’s a fast-paced operation that works cross-functionally with teams across Amazon globally, and is driven by data and performance indicators. The Sr Manufacturing Engineer will be responsible for applying design for X principles to influence product designs and transition a wide range of robotic solutions from design to production for Amazon’s recently acquired Boulder-based Canvas Technology. We are seeking a talented and motivated Manufacturing Engineer with a proven track record of implementing best-in-class test techniques and processes within a complex supply chain. This role will report to AR’s Manager of Technical Operations, Manufacturing Engineering. You will work cross-functionally with Canvas Technology and AR to develop suppliers, manage product lifecycle changes, lead product quality improvement projects and drive technical root cause for supplier defects. The successful candidate will be capable of making wide-ranging business decisions on behalf of the organization and willing to “roll up sleeves and do what needs to get done” to consistently deliver results.Responsibilities:· Provide design for X guidance/feedback on electromechanical designs.· Guide best practices on manufacturing tolerances using GD&amp;T.· Launch tooling with accelerated schedules. Assess project risk.· Review external production processes, identify risk and mitigate.· Qualify production processes based on dimensional data, control plans.· Drive internal and external PFMEA reviews.· Solve technical problems across a broad set of manufacturing commodities.· Mentor team members and design engineers.· Propose design changes that will enhance product sustainability.· Evaluate and approve product Engineering Changes Orders (ECOs).· Evaluate production, supplier and field failures for root cause analysis and resolution.· Up to 25% travel required, with periodic flexibility, as needed.</description>
      <location>US, CO, Boulder</location>
      <category>Hardware Development</category>
      <job_id>977773</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Robotics LLC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>e5c417a11930bc3490d49a7874a77da8</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977768/sr-advertising-sales-manager</job_url>
      <title>Sr Advertising Sales Manager</title>
      <description>Amazon Advertising operates at the intersection of eCommerce and advertising, offering a rich array of digital display advertising solutions with the goal of helping our customers find and discover anything they want to buy. We help advertisers reach Amazon customers on the Amazon owned and operated sites, on other high quality sites across the web, and on millions of tablets and mobile devices. We start with the customer and work backwards in everything we do, including advertising. If you’re interested in joining a rapidly growing team working to build a unique, world-class advertising group with a relentless focus on the customer, you’ve come to the right place.As a Senior Advertising Sales Manager on our Ad Sales team in Mexico, you will use your experience selling digital advertising solutions to large advertisers and their ad agencies in Mexico to successfully grow and scale the domestic revenues. Through client-side and agency relationships, a consultative approach and understanding of the digital advertising landscape, you will act as a strategic partner to your assigned brands or clients and sell a broad range of advertising solutions that will ensure that their business goals are met. You will further use your cold-calling, networking and prospecting skills to identify, develop and manage new accounts or brands that will complement our existing roster and help you reach your personal revenue targets. As an individual contributor, you’ll be supported by our operations team and will benefit from working alongside the leadership team that has charted our explosive growth.Job Location: Mexico City, Mexico</description>
      <location>MX, MEX, Mexico City</location>
      <category>Sales, Advertising, &amp; Account Management</category>
      <job_id>977768</job_id>
      <company_name>Servicios Comerciales Amazon M</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>4153bf5e1e7f965f614b21b67122ba48</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977767/software-development-engineer-in-test-ad-tech-search-experience</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer in Test, Ad Tech Search Experience</title>
      <description>Amazon is building a world class advertising business and defining and delivering a collection of self-service performance advertising products that drive discovery and sales of merchandise. Our products are strategically important to our Retail and Marketplace businesses, driving long-term growth. We deliver billions of ad impressions and millions of clicks daily and are breaking fresh ground to create world-class products. We are highly motivated, collaborative and fun-loving with an entrepreneurial spirit and bias for action. With a broad mandate to experiment and innovate, we are growing at an unprecedented rate with a seemingly endless range of new ideas and opportunities.We are looking for an experienced SDE-T for the Sponsored Products Supply team. Sponsored Products helps merchants, retail vendors and brand owners grow incremental sales of their products on Amazon through native product advertising. The Sponsored Products Supply team works on complex engineering, optimization, econometric and user-experience problems in order to deliver relevant product ads on Amazon search pages world-wide.As an SDE-T in our team, you will work closely with engineers to:· Define test plans to support our software launches· Work with the development and testing team to further increase our test coverage· Design and build automation frameworks that allow our developers write automated tests more efficiently· Lead automation efforts, and explore new test automation tools and methods· Work directly with Developers, SDE-Ts, Product Managers, and TPMs to ensure quality of our productsWe are just getting started. Come join us as we innovate and launch exciting new products and services in the coming year!Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer - Female/Minority/Disability/Veteran/Gender Identity/Sexual Orientation.#sspasv</description>
      <location>US, CA, Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>977767</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>4e84510b6b95abbdaf3a86e2627b332e</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977743/sr-technical-recruiter</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Technical Recruiter</title>
      <description>At Amazon.com, we're working to be the most customer-centric company on earth. To get there, we need exceptionally talented, bright, and driven people. The Operations Technology Recruiting team is looking for a Recruiter to support a growing Group which is a part of a larger global Operations Technology Team. This team is responsible for exempt hiring in North America and focuses on roles based in several software Development Centers, Seattle, Austin, Toronto, Bay Area, etc. This role will primarily focus on Software Development Recruitment. As a Recruiter for this team you will lead and mentor recruiters, cultivate talent sourcing channels, develop relationships with a variety of stakeholders and close searches against aggressive deadlines. This role will also require resource management of both internal and external sourcing partners.Amazon business is dependent on our ability to be Customer Obsessed. If you thrive in a fast paced environment, working on a highly visible team with dynamic business leaders, and have a passion for building great teams that directly impact the business and the customer’s experience, we look forward to receiving your application.In this role, you will be responsible for talent attraction strategies against a timeline and utilize experience setting benchmarks and metrics.Our Recruiters thrive in an innovative, fast-paced environment, can roll up their sleeves, work hard, have fun, and get the job done. You will have the opportunity to draw on your extensive knowledge of Talent Acquisition and functional areas of the business; and forge dynamic relationships with business leaders, hiring managers and HR business partners. You will perform candidate generation, client/account management, prioritize your time in an extremely fast-paced environment, push back when needed, and provide amazing customer service.Core Responsibilities:· Partner with hiring teams to build effective sourcing, assessment, and closing approaches with an ability to manage customer/partner expectations through a deep understanding of return on investment.· Recruit passive candidates and gauge chemistry of candidates for fit and motivation rather than simply sell a role.· Build and maintain network of potential candidates through proactive market research and on-going relationship management; conduct in-depth interviews of potential candidates, demonstrating ability to anticipate hiring manager preferences through high interview-to-offer ratios.· Recommend ideas and strategies related to recruitment that will contribute to the long-range growth of the company, implementing any new processes and fine tuning standard processes for recruiting that fits within Amazon's mission to deliver the highest quality results to the customer.· Articulate in writing recruiting plans with deliverables, timelines and a formal tracking process.· Interview candidates within the framework of the position specification. Screen, interview and prepare an ideal candidate slate within an appropriate and consistent timeline.· Work with the business, HRBP, and Compensation to determine appropriate salary ranges and negotiate compensation with candidates.· Participate in special projects/recruiting initiatives including assessment of best practices in interviewing techniques, leveraging of internal sources of talent and identification of top performers for senior-level openings.</description>
      <location>US, TX, Austin</location>
      <category>Human Resources</category>
      <job_id>977743</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>fd53646c66efa76c942e65100fee9103</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977720/instructional-designer-amazon-selling-partner-support</job_url>
      <title>Instructional Designer - Amazon Selling Partner Support</title>
      <description>Opportunity with Amazon Selling Partner Support Learning Experience. Are you a learning professional who is People Obsessed, passionate about growing resilient, bar-raising talent that evolves with business needs? Fearless? Not afraid to ask audacious questions to ignite potential? Then, the Amazon Selling Partner Support Learning Experience team is the place for you!This role will build our next generation learning programs for Amazon’s Selling Partner Support Associates. These Associates serve the Selling Partners who provide a significant portion of Amazon’s amazing product selection. You will prepare frontline associates through the design and build of face-to-face and virtual learning programs that work anywhere, anytime.We believe that every employee interaction builds trust, increases performance and drives engagement to enable extraordinary Selling Partner experiences. We are looking for Learning Experience Designers who feels the same way.Engage. Scale. Amplify.As a Learning Experience Designer you will design, build, enhance, and maintain our onboarding and up-skill learning programs on a global scale. Your design toolbox includes traditional classroom, elearning, self-directed, and virtual learning methods focused on delivering real performance outcomes. In this role, you will ensure that our programs create an exceptional learning experience that produces expected business outcomes. You will transform our programs through technology, so we can easily scale to meet our Associates’ needs worldwide. You will champion the Associates’ voice to shape how they learn and develop their skills on behalf of our Sellers and Vendors.The Learning Experience Designer will:· Design and develop bar-raising learning associate-facing programs using ADDIE and AGILE methodologies.· Build elearning, instructor-led classroom and virtual classroom programs, performance assessments, surveys, and self-directed learning programs.· Partner with operations and program leaders to align our learning programs with the expected business outcomes.· Optimize the use of learning technologies that help us scale.· Embed data collection and feedback mechanisms throughout our learning solutions to generate data-driven, actionable insights into the Associate Learning Experience. Lead efforts to drive continuous performance improvement from those insights.· Design and transform our learning programs from classroom-based instructor-led training to blended virtual programs.· Communicate progress and opportunities through daily huddles and weekly, monthly, and quarterly business reviews.· Analyze performance data to determine performance and learning objectives that deliver expected business results from new hire and cross-trained Associates.Amazon.com is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer – Minority / Female / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Leadership Development &amp; Training</category>
      <job_id>977720</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>0d0bb15c12dde88f5930d41373db50ee</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977624/partner-support-and-solutions-emea-trainer</job_url>
      <title>Partner Support and Solutions EMEA Trainer</title>
      <description>Partner Support and Solutions EMEA Trainer is responsible for training delivery, coordination and reporting for new hire, cross training, refresher, and feature launch training for our Selling Partner Associates, and thus is accountable for producing positive training results.The Trainer coordinates directly with senior business owners (site leader, operations managers, team managers, etc), Regional and Global Academy Managers, other Seller Support Trainers, leads, training mentors and instructional designers to ensure all trainings are conducted on-time and with sufficient resources and facilities.Coordinate Training including communicating with appropriate business owners: seller support team leaders; Global Learning &amp; Performance Manager; other Seller Support Trainers; subject matter experts and Associates to ensure all trainings are conducted on-time and with sufficient resources and facilities.Facilitate blended learning training classes for new hires, new skills (cross-training), feature launches, and refreshers as necessary in our sites. The person hired for this trainer role must be able to use the learning management system and test practice environment.Learning Plan development and implementation for low-performing associates, including coaching/mentoring as needed.Site Training Administration, including administering testing and certification, managing the training calendar, reporting on work outcomes and impact, scheduling, and partnering with site leadership to deliver all curriculum development, training and other learning intervention requests. This role will also include use of surveys, quizzes, performance metrics and other available tools to evaluate the effectiveness of training and assess new Associate learning and skill development.Overall, the Partner Support and Solutions EMEA Trainer will be responsible for driving high quality training provided to Amazon employees and play a significant role in the development of a successful, effective global technical support team. Shift Work Required - This position will primarily deliver evening and night shift training.</description>
      <location>ES, B, Barcelona</location>
      <category>Leadership Development &amp; Training</category>
      <job_id>977624</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Spain Services, S.L.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>82084f962c940000e13168f4d5a03657</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977623/dceo-cluster-manager-singapore</job_url>
      <title>DCEO Cluster Manager, Singapore</title>
      <description>DCEO Manager SingaporeResponsible for the management of Data Center Engineering Operations (DCEO) within Amazon owned Data Centers or Amazon leased Data Center areas within third party Colocation facilities; including risk management and mitigation, corrective and preventative maintenance of critical infrastructure, vendor management and metric reporting.Responsibilities:1. Management and leadership of DCEO Engineering Team2. Establish performance benchmarks, conduct analyses, and prepare reports on all aspects of the critical facility operations and maintenance3. Responsible for the on-site management of shift technicians, senior shift technicians, sub-contractors and vendors, ensuring that all work performed is in accordance with established practices and procedures.4. Manage relationship with third party Colocation providers and their facility staff5. Responsible for the operation of and management of both routine and emergency services on a variety of critical systems such as: switchgear, generators, UPS systems, power distribution equipment, chillers, cooling towers, computer room air handlers, building monitoring systems, etc6. Data Center capacity planning and reporting7. May assist in the design and build out of new facilities8. May assist in projects to increase current Facility efficiency9. Work with IT managers and other business leaders to coordinate projects, manage capacity, and optimize plant safety, performance, reliability and efficiency10. Deliver quality service and ensure all customer demands are met11. Procurement for DCEO related expenditure12. Responsible for asset and inventory management13. Assist in recruiting efforts</description>
      <location>SG, Singapore</location>
      <category>Operations, IT, &amp; Support Engineering</category>
      <job_id>977623</job_id>
      <company_name>Amzn Asia-PacificResources SGP</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>1ddf9170fd8e7a3613758736742fc573</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977622/sr-product-manager</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Product Manager</title>
      <description>Are you interested in building large-scale services that will make it simpler for publishers around the world to sell their books on Kindle?The Kindle Content team is looking for an innovative, results-oriented Product Manager to drive our Advantage program. Advantage is flagship This includes setting vision and strategy for Advantage publishers, defining the overall product and experience for our enterprise customers, and partnering with development teams on critical feature developments.Advantage is a global self-service consignment program for all physical media categories (books, DVDs, music, software, and video games ) that allows Amazon Retail to profitably carry long-tail selection. With self-service vendor registration and standard terms, the Advantage program allows Amazon to cost-effectively do business with vendors (authors, publishers, studios, artists and labels) of all sizes. Advantage is a billion dollar business operating in multiple marketplaces WW with Advantage vendors currently use the Advantage Central (AC) platform to conduct their business.The ideal candidate works effectively in a cross-functional environment and is comfortable communicating with both technical and business stakeholders. This person has a history of delivering high quality, web-based applications and/or portals that serve hundreds of thousands of users worldwide. This person also uses data to guide decision-making, has strong business judgement, and can solve complicated problems with simple, elegant solutions.Key responsibilities include:· Establish the product vision, goals, and key KPIs for success.· Define product requirements and drive iterative development cycle with engineers, designers, and other stakeholders.· Oversee product user interface design, usability testing, customer research, launch, and marketing.· Manage bottlenecks, resolve escalations, and drive key feature and resource trade-offs.Serve as a key member of the Content Acquisition team, helping define and deliver strategy around acquisition and growth programs.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Non-Tech</category>
      <job_id>977622</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>880c0bbe804f67124c3020a6d3b2946b</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977616/senior-product-manager-technical</job_url>
      <title>Senior Product Manager - Technical</title>
      <description>AWS Elemental is the world-leader in video processing products. We are looking for an experienced Product Management professional to drive evolution of our service offerings.What you’ll do:· Work with customers, engineering teams, external partners, and the AWS Elemental management team to set product development priorities· Define new features and functionality in the AWS product offerings using the successful Amazon “working backwards” process· Listen to customers and potential customers to deeply understand their needs of the software· Create a vision and roadmap for the evolution of video· Define critical software features in AWS Elemental software· Author documents that shape our strategic investments· Present new product information directly to customers, either in-person, or through digital delivery.· Develop your understand of the world of video compression and video delivery to better support our customers</description>
      <location>US, OR, Portland</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Technical</category>
      <job_id>977616</job_id>
      <company_name>Elemental Technologies LLC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>ed759292be1f75681f073663cded2262</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:16:13 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/977615/sourcing-recruiter</job_url>
      <title>Sourcing Recruiter</title>
      <description>The Role:The Amazon Devices recruiting team is seeking a talented results oriented Technical Sourcer with a passion for delighting the client and candidate. You will work with a close-knit recruiting team. Your focus will be on driving recruiting strategies along with candidate generation and closing of candidates in partnership with your clients. This is a great opportunity to be part of a team focused on making an impact on the business, recruiting for innovative talent.As a Technical Sourcer you will partner with the business teams to execute against our hiring goals for a dynamic, growing business.</description>
      <location>US, CA, Sunnyvale</location>
      <category>Human Resources</category>
      <job_id>977615</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/search.json?base_query=&amp;city=&amp;country=&amp;county=&amp;facets%5B%5D=location&amp;facets%5B%5D=business_category&amp;facets%5B%5D=category&amp;facets%5B%5D=schedule_type_id&amp;facets%5B%5D=employee_class&amp;facets%5B%5D=normalized_location&amp;facets%5B%5D=job_function_id&amp;latitude=&amp;loc_group_id=&amp;loc_query=United+States&amp;longitude=&amp;offset=2850&amp;query_options=&amp;radius=24km&amp;region=&amp;result_limit=10&amp;sort=relevant</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>8b53f751c33849c0f52b84aa53539387</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979745/business-development-manager-training-us-southeast</job_url>
      <title>Business Development Manager - Training US-Southeast</title>
      <description>This role can be based in Tampa, FL or Atlanta, GA.The Training &amp; Certification Business Development Manager (BDM) is accountable for the development of Training Services revenue in the corporate and public segments. The BDM will develop strategic segment plans, sales goals, strategies and forecasting. They will build &amp; maintain a pipeline of training opportunities and provide regular forecasts / business reviews to senior managementHe/she will work with account teams to identify training opportunities; develop relationships with key accounts; create training plans and proposals, execute contracts (Training Order Forms), oversee training plan deliverables; present learning plans and training services to multiple levels at AWS customers and partners, including senior management and executives.The BDM will create and nurture relationships with sales and partner development teams supporting them to drive training business. They will conduct sales enablement activities that help them understand AWS Training &amp; Certification offerings, how to position them with their customers and partners and keep them up to speed on new programs, policies and procedures.The BDM will work closely with clients to determine training requirements, conduct training needs assessments and build detailed training proposals and plans to accelerate adoption of AWS Services. They will maintain a strong relationship with customers and partners to ensure flawless execution of training plans.</description>
      <location>US, GA, Atlanta</location>
      <category>Leadership Development &amp; Training</category>
      <job_id>979745</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>7b34e787a9198ad19a70cd959073059c</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979743/sr-customer-solutions-manager-global-accounts</job_url>
      <title>Sr. Customer Solutions Manager, Global Accounts</title>
      <description>At Amazon Web Services (AWS) we are leading the cloud revolution. As a Customer Solutions Manager you will work with the largest and most complex enterprises in the world, to enable their multi-year journey to the cloud. In this new, highly visible, role you will ensure that all AWS teams work together effectively and efficiently to deliver for the customer.Role &amp; ResponsibilitiesYou will be a trusted advisor to your customer. You will leverage your program management, technical, organizational, and transformation expertise to understand your customer's business and strategic goals, translate them into an executable plan, and drive the implementation to success by working with the customer, AWS, and our partners. You will understand your customers' biggest IT challenges, and provide prescriptive guidance, based on AWS best practices, to guide them through the obstacles.You will take end-to-end ownership of a diverse range of projects and initiatives, utilizing your communication skills to interface with and influence a broad range of multi disciplinary teams (sales, solutions architecture, support, product, professional services, partners). The Customer Solutions Manager role is responsible for cloud transformational programs (technical, operational, organizational, education) that span across traditional IT teams and business units.With a deep understanding of your customer's business vision, culture and processes, you will be your customer's voice within AWS, ensuring that their needs are accurately communicated to AWS leadership, product, and engineering teams. You will evangelize AWS services and influence customers to adopt the right solution at the right time. You should be passionate about delivering a great customer experience by deploying AWS solutions, driving innovation, and delivering successful migration programs.In addition to your customer facing responsibilities, you will help shape the rapidly growing Customer Solutions Management function, where your passion to define and implement standard processes, methodologies, and tools will be highly valued.Successful candidates will have a technical program management background, be detail driven, and have experience in managing virtual teams to deliver complex programs. You will be a passionate and proven leader with the ability to gain stakeholder buy-in, communicate confidently at both the executive and project team level, and collaborate with a wide range of technical and non-technical teams, regardless of geographical or organizational boundaries. You will be a natural problem solver with a cool head that can deal with ambiguity and work autonomously to drive the deliver results for your customer.Must be able/willing to travel up to 40% (some global)</description>
      <location>US, CA, East Palo Alto</location>
      <category>Project/Program/Product Management--Technical</category>
      <job_id>979743</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon Web Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>af7499503947cd1000bf34daa26107f9</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979737/technical-trainer</job_url>
      <title>Technical Trainer</title>
      <description>Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world.Low cost. Instant Elasticity. Open &amp; Flexible. Secure.To meet the growing demand for AWS Services around the globe, we need exceptionally talented, bright, and driven people. If you have strong IT infrastructure and/or programming experience, and can communicate highly technical concepts to audiences at different stages in the AWS journey, we’d like to speak with you.We are looking for a dynamic, organized self-starter to join our Training Team.Here's your chance to work as a Technical Trainer on a newly formed team, with high visibility and significant customer impact. The successful candidate is an experienced technical trainer, ideally with hands-on experience with Amazon Web Services and/or in-depth knowledge of software architecture and virtualization technologies.In this role, you will deliver training content to developers, administrators, architects, and partners to drive adoption and usage of AWS services. You’ll have an opportunity to combine a passion for teaching, with enthusiasm for technology, to drive learning and establish positive customer relationships. You will have excellent communication skills and proven technology training experience.· Deliver classroom and on-line training to customers and partners.· Assist in developing and maintaining training content, lab exercises, presentations, and accompanying materials.· Mentor internal and external authorized instructors as part of a train the trainer program.· Capture and share best-practice knowledge across the training community.· Understand the AWS market segments, customer base, and industry verticals.</description>
      <location>IN, KA, Bengaluru</location>
      <category>Leadership Development &amp; Training</category>
      <job_id>979737</job_id>
      <company_name>AISPL - Karnataka</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>19c516821e775cfa56a6d785b4e703a4</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979735/senior-security-engineer-hardware</job_url>
      <title>Senior Security Engineer - Hardware</title>
      <description>Help us protect not only the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud computing environment but all of our customers as well! Since 2006, our great team at AWS has been enabling our customers to bring great ideas to life in ways that aren’t possible in traditional IT environments. With AWS you can flexibly harness compute, storage, security, and other services from across the globe as your business demands them.AWS Security is on the cutting edge of many security issues for a wide variety of platforms and technologies including cloud services, Internet of things (IoT), identity and access management, mobile devices, virtualization and custom hardware, all operating at massive scale. Similarly, our highly collaborative team is committed to each team member’s growth as our business grows.As a part of the Emerging Technologies Security Engineering group, we help AWS launch brand new products and invest in emerging technologies securely. We are looking for a technically deep Senior Security Engineer to help secure our foundational platforms with an emphasis on hardware. You will be responsible for conducting security reviews, threat modeling, developing tooling that will help detect security issues at scale and hands on security evaluations (penetration testing).The successful candidate must be comfortable diving into complex engineering discussions, and leveraging deep security expertise to ensure proper risk assessment and threat analysis is performed. You will provide crystal-clear technical direction and risk mitigation guidance for diverse engineering and business leaders at all levels.By applying your hard-earned years of practical security engineering expertise in projects related to securing hardware, you will literally shape the future of cloud computing.A Senior Security Engineer at Amazon is expected to be strong in multiple domains and provide significant contributions to the AWS Security team and to multiple groups throughout Amazon. Security engineers are expected to develop elegant solutions to complex business problems and apply appropriate technologies while following security engineering best practices. You are also expected to mentor more junior engineers and be a security thought leader for the organization.A Senior Security Engineer should foster constructive dialogue and seek resolution when confronted with discordant views. Engineers in this role are expected to participate fully in the planning of the Emerging Technologies Security Engineering group's work and constantly seek opportunities for process improvement. They should also have a deep understanding of at least one specialty for which they are a sought out resource (both within AWS Security and by groups throughout Amazon), while having an understanding of the application of information security in a broad range of technical areas.A successful candidate will need a combination of troubleshooting, technical, and communication skills, as well as the ability to handle a mix of disparate tasks which may include project and software development work. This role will provide career growth opportunities as you gain new security skills in the course of your duties.Responsibilities:· Security reviews for hardware including servers and devices· Penetration testing &amp; vulnerability research· Threat modeling· Security training and outreach to internal development teams· Security guidance documentation· Assistance with recruiting activities</description>
      <location>US</location>
      <category>Systems, Quality, &amp; Security Engineering</category>
      <job_id>979735</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>811c4c3f89412c1a17a92b18c6f99100</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979734/data-scientist</job_url>
      <title>Data Scientist</title>
      <description>At Amazon we strive to be earth’s most customer centric company and data is a foundational component to making this happen. In this role you will be responsible for navigating this wealth of data and turning it into actionable and insightful information for business partners in order to deliver better products and services to our customers.Are you curious about new platforms and technologies and have a desire to deliver world-class customer service? Are you excited by the idea of owning a problem and innovating on behalf of customers? Can you deal with ambiguity and keep up with the pace of a company whose cycles are measured in weeks, not years?Amazon introduced the first Kindle in 2007 — at that time, it offered 90,000 eBooks and sold out 5.5 hours after the announcement. Since then, we have expanded to become the best-selling e-reader family in the world. We have gone beyond Kindle with our powerhouse Fire tablets, built for work and play with our Fire operating system. For streaming media lovers, we have created Amazon Fire TV, Fire TV Stick, and Fire TV Edition with voice search. Fire TV devices come with access to 500,000 movies, TV shows, and tens of thousands of channels, and apps. In 2014, we introduced Amazon Echo and Alexa, the voice service that powers Echo and other devices so customers can play music, control their smart homes, and get information, news, weather, and more using just their voice. Alexa is now integrated with over 20,000 third party devices from 3,500 brands. Alexa has 50,000 skills and developers in 180 countries. Want to know more, join our team!As a BIE on our Digital, Device and Alexa Support team (D2AS), you will utilize big data technologies such as Redshift and Tableau to develop standardized reporting and analysis that enable leaders to take action on findings and recommendations.Overall Responsibilities Include:· Create and maintain data visualizations that inform and engage business partners on key metrics.· · Data mine key performance indicators to discover root causes for customer dissatisfaction.· · Conduct trending analysis to identify opportunities, highlight strengths, and provide recommended corrective actions.· · Perform complex data analysis in support of ad-hoc reporting requests.· · Develop programs, methodologies, and reports for analyzing and presenting data.· · Supporting cross-functional teams on day-to-day execution of projects and process improvements.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Data Science</category>
      <job_id>979734</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>6ce2e9d81c2781cfee78dddd93d6cb7c</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979732/hr-business-partner</job_url>
      <title>HR Business Partner</title>
      <description>At Amazon, we're working to be the most customer-centric company on earth. To get there, we need exceptionally talented, bright, and driven people. If you'd like to help us build the place to find and buy anything online, this is your chance to make history. We are looking for a dynamic, organized self-starter to join our Human Resources department as an HR Business Partner in one of our North America Fulfillment Centers.The HR Business Partner is both a strategic and hands-on role that provides full cycle Human Resources support to our initiatives around flexible fulfillment centers. The role is critical in executing our people initiatives, providing great internal customer support, and driving HR functional excellence and process improvement.Successful candidates will demonstrate:• The ability to understand business goals and recommend new approaches, policies and procedures to effect continual improvements in business objectives, productivity and development of HR within the company• A true hands-on approach as well as the ability to successfully monitor the "pulse" of the employees to ensure a high level of employee engagement• Experience with rapid and complex changing work environment• Passion for innovative HR solutions and process improvement; Demonstrated experience driving processes improvements and specific skills in Kaizen methodologies preferred• Strong project management skills; ability to lead projects at a network level to influence and obtain buy-in, and then drive execution and achievement of the right results• Success in creating and driving effective employee relations, retention and reward programs• The ability to be comfortable with high volume workload and not be afraid to "roll up your sleeves"• A strong solutions focus and be comfortable working in an environment which demands strong deliverables along with the ability to identify problems and drive appropriate solutions• Strong internal and external customer service focus• The ability to manage multiple priorities simultaneously - orientated on results• Excellent organizational and interpersonal skills• Shift flexibility is critical in our environment, to meet the needs of our 24/7 environment; shifts can change as business dictates.</description>
      <location>CA, ON, Milton</location>
      <category>Human Resources</category>
      <job_id>979732</job_id>
      <company_name>AMZN CAN Fulfillment Svcs, ULC</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>46a6447bd802d08bd103dcfae53dc6e6</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979719/technical-program-manager</job_url>
      <title>Technical Program Manager</title>
      <description>Amazon FreeTime brings together all types of content that kids and parents love including books, games, Audible books, educational apps, videos, and Alexa skills. It provides peace of mind for parents with parental controls and a world of fun for kids to choose from thousands of the most popular titles and age-appropriate content. Here's more information: http://www.amazon.com/freetime.The Catalog Delivery and Personalization team stand on the front line of FreeTime, serving thousands of requests per second to millions of Amazon devices. Come help define our forward-looking architecture and strategy for latency, caching, transactionality, and data federation at scale.In this role, you will leverage your hands-on project management skills, deep technical expertise, and excellent leadership skills to take high level/ambiguous ideas and turn them into tangible products for parents and kids. You will work with other FreeTime TPMs to create lightweight and agile processes that ensure consistent, high quality projects are delivered on time. You will influence the product roadmaps of our teams and others within Amazon to unify our products and to provide value to our customers. You will think globally when designing and building the software, ensuring the software is evolving in the right long term direction while bringing value to customers iteratively.The right candidate will possess a strong program management background, will have demonstrated experience leading medium to large projects, and will have a well-rounded technical background in current development technologies. You must be able to thrive and succeed in an entrepreneurial environment, and not be hindered by ambiguity or competing priorities. This means you are not only able to develop and drive high-level strategic initiatives, but can also roll up your sleeves, dig in and get the job done.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>979719</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>384e6a3dfd89cf220818e978dd7e32cf</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979717/data-scientist</job_url>
      <title>Data Scientist</title>
      <description>Are you passionate about understanding customer behavior, explaining actions and measuring outcomes to inform and optimize Amazon programs? Do you get excited about guiding the business on what makes shopping easier, personalized and effective for every Amazon customer? Amazon Assistant is changing the way customers shop online and provides contextually relevant, predictive and personalized shopping help whenever and wherever the customer is. Amazon Assistant brings Amazon to customers on any device to offer true shopping assistance anywhere they shop off-Amazon.We are looking for a highly motivated Data Scientist who can help ensure our experience on Amazon Assistant and onsite is creating long-term value for our customers. This person will be responsible for architecting insights and systems to anticipate which features will drive more traffic to Amazon overall and for upper funnel discovery and inspiration. This person will also be responsible for designing experiments and devising frameworks that measure the short-term and long-term impact of our marketing activities, product features and CX on customers’ shopping habits, spending patterns and price perception. Finally, this person would also derive insights using our existing data and experiments to inform new innovation and direction for Amazon Assistant and internal partner teams.The ideal candidate will be an expert in the areas of data science, machine learning and statistics, having hands-on experience with multiple improvement initiatives as well as balancing technical and business judgment to make the right decisions about technology, models and methodologies. You will leverage data, experimental design, and analytics to help define new ways to evaluate, visualize and predict to understand outcome and decisions on how to improve customer engagement across customer lifecycle segments. The candidate needs experience with data science / business intelligence, analytics, and reporting systems while striving for simplicity, and demonstrating significant creativity and high judgment backed by statistical proof.The ideal candidate should have deep expertise in the design, creation, management, and business use of large datasets. You should have excellent business and communication skills to be able to work with business owners to develop and define key business questions, and use appropriate statistical and econometric techniques to derive insights and recommendations to leadership. You should excel at bringing large datasets together to answer business questions and drive change.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Data Science</category>
      <job_id>979717</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>9346c775c3b08a76d01d29cd4acdfcfe</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979716/principal-program-manager-aitc-communications</job_url>
      <title>Principal Program Manager, AITC Communications</title>
      <description>Amazon in the Community (AITC) seeks an experienced, self-motivated leader to create a marketing strategy, build program brand(s), create global systems, and help communicate internally and externally. As a senior leader filling a new role on a young team, you will accelerate internal and external adoption of AITC programs and build awareness of our stories and impact.AITC’s “customers” are the global Amazon employees we engage and the people who benefit from our programs such as Amazon Future Engineer and Disaster Relief by Amazon. However, we engage with a broad array of people who need to be aware of our work including Amazon employees, nonprofit/nongovernmental organizations, Amazon’s customers, civic leaders, elected officials, and community members. This role has global responsibility and will work closely with the full AITC team and our colleagues throughout the company – especially in PR, Internal Comms, HR, and Public Policy.The ideal candidate will have demonstrated leadership skills and high-level of experience in: 1/defining strategy and brand; 2/building systems and playbooks; 3/crafting messaging, talking points, and presentations; 4 / setting data-driven methods to determine impact; and 5/managing in-kind contributors and consultants.The ideal candidate will work independently while balancing the need to act quickly with sound judgement and set and drive company-wide strategy and adoption. This candidate will roll up their sleeves on a small and growing high-influence team. The position will report to the global Director of Amazon in the Community.CORE RESPONSIBILITILITIES:· Lead marketing and strategic communications for all AITC programs providing an overall strategy and playbooks and consulting to individual programs and global AITC employees.· Manage internal and external presence of Amazon in the Community.· Develop messaging and write content to inform constituents of AITC activities.· Create performance indicators and measures of success that drive ongoing improvements that guide the future as much as they assess the past.· Identify opportunities and coordinate closely with internal communications, public relations, HR, and public policy teams.· Determine and manage paid consultants, employee volunteers, and in-kind contributions from other Amazon marketing and communications teams.· Determine needed technology solutions (such as marketing automation or CRM tools) and manage implementation.· Advocate for cultural and diversity interests of employees and communities globally.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
      <job_id>979716</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
<record>
<uniq_id>19745a7b740b84943c3315ced8a2b4be</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2019-11-15 00:17:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <job_url>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/jobs/979714/software-development-engineer-ii</job_url>
      <title>Software Development Engineer II</title>
      <description>The Amazon Checkout Platform team seeks a creative software development engineer who treats software development as a craft, cares deeply about our customers, and takes great pride in both the technical and business contributions of their work. We are a growing team building services and frameworks that power the mission critical Checkout experience on Amazon retail websites world-wide. This platform is used by thousands of developers across the company to delight hundreds of millions of customers across the world with innovative checkout experiences.We offer you the opportunity to build multi-tiered, low latency, highly resilient distributed systems at scale. You will play a leading role in building solutions that make a huge, measurable impact to the shopping experience. You will build solutions that can process large volumes of data, have lightning quick response times and make the checkout process ridiculously fast and simple.The ideal candidate will have excellent technical design, problem solving and communication skills and be comfortable interacting with technical and non-technical stakeholders at all levels. In addition, the ability to work backwards and think from a customer perspective is crucial.</description>
      <location>US, WA, Seattle</location>
      <category>Software Development</category>
      <job_id>979714</job_id>
      <company_name>Amazon.com Services, Inc.</company_name>
</record>
</page>
</root>
